Guide to the Duke Family papers on the Duke Farms residence, 1859-2004 and undated RL.01437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectural Records, 1897-1992 and undated
  - Duke Farms Surveys, Roads, Fields, 1900-1937, 1951-1984 and undated
    - General Property Key Map of Dukes Parkway (County Route 16-S-1) Showing Existing Right of Way and Parcels to be Acquired, Sheet 2 of 3. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1967 Jun 6. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - General Property Key Map of Dukes Parkway (County Route 16-S-1) Showing Existing Right of Way and Parcels to be Acquired, Sheet 3 of 3. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1967 Jun 6. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - Plan and Profile of South Branch Road. F.J. Hubbard. 1912 Jun. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - [Plan and Profile of South Branch Road]. [F.J. Hubbard]. [1912 Jun]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - [Plan and Profile of South Branch Road]. [F.J. Hubbard]. [1912 Jun]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - Plan and Details of Proposed Roadway Improvements (1 of 3). Raritan Valley Engineering/ S.C.M. 1964 Jul 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - Plan and Details of Roadway Improvements [Details 1-6] (2 of 3). Raritan Valley Engineering/ S.C.M. 1964 Jul 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - Plan and Details of Roadway Improvements [Details 7-13] (3 of 3). Raritan Valley Engineering/ S.C.M. 1964 Jul 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F1)
    - Various Soil Classes Masp. undated. Photocopy with ink. (Oversize-folder C1D7F2)
    - Olghart Farm Acreage Approx for Lease Purposes. undated. 1980. Colored markers, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Topographical Map of Ground West of Mansion. Louis L. Miller. 1931 Dec. Ink. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Soils and Buildings, Map Showing Acreage of Various Lots Situated in the Duke Estate. Includes original and various renditions such as exterior boundary line of estate woods, rentals, plantings, and proposed roads. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1973 Feb 1; revised 1973 Feb 2. Diazo, CAD drawing on film. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Soils & Buildings, Map Showing Acreage of Various Lots Situated in the Duke Estate. Includes outer bounds, farms, and crops. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1973 Feb 27. Pencil, diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Map Showing Acreage of Various Lots Situated in the Duke Estate. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1969 Dec 10. Diazo, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Duke Farms Hillsboro Township, New Jersey, Water Lines, 1911 & 1960. Tectonic Associates. 1963 Jan 3. Diazo with marker. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Preliminary Sketch of Proposed New Driveway and Entrance to Duke Gardens Foundation. Tectonic Associates/ R.V.E. 1962 Jan 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Plan and Profile of Proposed New Driveway and Entrance to Duke Gardens Foundation. Tectonic Associates. 1962 Mar 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F4)
    - Map of Survey Lands to be Conveyed to Doris Duke. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1968 Sep 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F8)
    - Map Showing Addition to the Duke Property Hillsborough Township, Smerset County, New Jersey. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1969 Sep 3. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F8)
    - Map of Survey Lands to be Conveyed to Doris Duke, Tract Known as Tax Map Lot 1 & 1-A Block 1, 50. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1972 Dec 21. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D7F8)
    - Hillsborough Township Map and Directory. Hillsborough Republicans for Better Government. [circa 1980s]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D8F9a)
    - Hillsborough Township. Hillsborough Republicans for Better Government. [circa 1980s]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D8F9a)
    - List of County Officials. [circa 1980s]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D8F9a)
    - Map Showing Area Leased to the Animal Medical Center. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1973 Feb 1. Diazo, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D8F9a)
    - Delineation of Floodway and Flood Hazard Area. State of New Jersey Department of Conservation & Economic Development Division of Water Policy and Supply/Anderson, Nichols & Co. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D8F12)
    - General Property Key Map, U.S. Route 206 & Duke's Parkway, Showing Existing Right of Way & Parcels to be Acquired. Donald H. Stires. 1961 Jun. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - Proposed Jughandle. New Jersey State. Highway Dept. 1960 Jun 21. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - General Property Parcel Map, Route U.S. 206 (1953) Section 15, Amwell Road to Route 28, Showing Existing Right of Way and Parcels to be Acquired. New Jersey State. Highway Dept. 1961 Sep. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - Auten & New Centre Road Alignment to Rt 206. undated. Diazo with marker. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - Route 16-Section 5A Property Map showing Properties to be Acquired from Somerville to South Somerville Hillsboro Township - Somerset County. New Jersey State. Highway Dept. 1924 Nov; revised 1925 May. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - Proposed 206 Widening. undated. (Oversize-folder C2D2F3)
    - Hillsborough Township. F.E.H. 1944. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Road Map of Township of Hillsborough Somerset County, New Jersey. Van Note/Harvey Associates. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Hillsborough Township. Queale and Lynch. 1973. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - General Property Key Map, Route-31, Section-4, Somerville By-Pass. New Jersey State. Highway Dept. 1929 May. Blueprint, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Map of Lakes, Roads, Buildings & Water Mains [Partial]. Buckenham & Miller, landscape engineers. 1911 Jan. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Map of Lakes, Roads, Buildings & Water Mains [Partial]. Buckenham & Miller, landscape engineers. 1911 Jan. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Building Plot Plan. undated. Negative photostat. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - [Map of Area between 206, RR tracks, Raritan and Duke's Parkway West]. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Survey for Duke Farms and Raritan Water Power Company. Strait & Adams. 1937 Apr. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Map Showing Location of Raritan River. J. Doughtly, Jr. 1910 Dec. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Proposed Poles and Guy Anchors Located on State Highway Route #31. PSE&G. 1930 Jul 16. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C2D7F2)
    - Property Line Location, Lot 3, Block 142 Hillsborough Township, NJ. Donald H. Stires Associates/RLM/HEM. 1982 Oct 22. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Map of Survey, Block 50, Lot 1, Hillsborough Township, Somerset County, New Jersey. George Riehman/T.M./G.R. 1984 Nov 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 1. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 2. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 3. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 4. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 5. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 6. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Hillsborough Township Tax Map, 26. Aero Service Corporation. 1959 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Raritan Borough Tax Map. Aero Service Corporation/Cilo & Vilet. 1959 Jan 12; revised 1976 Nov. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Raritan Borough Tax Map. Aero Service Corporation/Cilo & Vilet. 1959 Jan 12; revised 1976 Nov. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Map of Survey Lengyel Property Tax Map, Lot 10 Block 144, Hillsborough Township, Somerset County, New Jersey. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1972 Jan 31. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F5)
    - Duke Farms. undated. Photography on paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - Map of Duke Farms Somerville, NJ. undated. White-lined paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - Map of Duke Farms Somerville, NJ. undated. White-lined paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], D-1. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], D-2. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], D-3. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], D-4. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], D-5. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], E-2. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - [Map of Duke Farms], E-3. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F6)
    - Utility Lines Added, D4. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, B1. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, B3. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, B4. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, C3. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, D2. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Utility Lines Added, D3. 1983 Aug 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F4)
    - Route I-95/695 Environmental Impact Statement. Richard H. Schindelar. 1966 Jan. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D8F7)
    - Aerial Photography Doris Duke Estate. undated. Photograph on paper. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7c)
    - Duke Farms. undated. Electrostatic print. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7c)
    - PL. & SPL. Aerial Cable Twp of Bridgewater, Twp of Hillsboro. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1937 Sep 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7c)
    - PL. & SPL. Aerial Cable Twp of Bridgewater. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1937 Sep 14. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7c)
    - Proposed New Roadway of New Center Road - Hillsborough Twp., Somerset County. 1944. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Sanitary Sewer Plans and Details to Service Certain Facilities of Duke Farms Within Tax Lot 1, Block 49. Richard H. Schindelar. 1993 Jan. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Standard Construction Details to Service Certain Facilities of Duke Farms Within Tax Lot 1, Block 49. Richard H. Schindelar. 1993 Jan. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Sanitary Sewer Testing Details to Service Certain Facilities of Duke Farms Within Tax Lot 1, Block 49. Richard H. Schindelar. 1993 Jan. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Pump Tank & Valve/Meter Pit Details to Service Certain Facilities of Duke Farms Within Tax Lot 1, Block 49. Richard H. Schindelar. 1993 Feb. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - [Block 48, Lot 3, Block 14, Lot 18, Block 150, Lot 1, 1A]. Richard H. Schindelar. 1997 Sep. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Somerset County Natural Resource Inventory, 1-10. Somerset County Planning Board. 1982 Fall. Poster. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - Geological Map of Raritan, NJ. US Dept of Army Corp of Engineers. 1955. Color print. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - [Various Maps of Duke Farms] Figures 1-9. Divney, Tung, Schwalbe. Undated. Color photocopy. (Oversize-folder DF32)
    - General Property Map - Route U.S. 206 (1953) Section 15J Amwell Road to Route 28 Parcel #3R20A. Louis Berger & Associates. 1953. Laser print. (Tube TU211)
    - General Property Map - Route U.S. 206 (1953) Section 15J Amwell Road to Route 28 Parcel #3R20B. Louis Berger & Associates. 1953. Laser print. (Tube TU211)
    - Aerial photography - Eas 3R 204. 1956 Oct 1. Photograph on paper. (Tube TU211)
    - Aerial photography - Eas 4R 61. 1956 Oct 5. Photograph on paper. (Tube TU211)
    - Conservation Plan Map. undated. Photograph on paper. (Tube TU211)
    - Aerial Photography. undated. Photograph on paper. (Tube TU211)
    - Map of Estate of J.B. Duke. L. Strassburger. 1900 Mar. Sepia diazo. (Tube TU300)
    - Map of Duke's Farms, Somerville, N.J. Buckenham & Miller, landscape engineers. 1905 Jan. Blueprint on linen. (Tube TU302)
    - Estate of J. B. Duke Esq., Somerville N.J. Buckenham & Miller, landscape engineers. 1905 Jan. Ferrogallic print on linen. (Tube TU302)
    - Map of Duke's Park, Somerville, N.J. Louis L. Miller. 1915 Jan. Reverse blueprint. (Tube TU303)
    - Map of the Doris Duke Estate, Hillsborough Township, N.J. Louis L. Miller. 1932. Positive photostat. (Tube TU303)
  - Miscellaneous, 1901-1994 and undated
    - Location Plan of McCready Road Duke Farms. Strait & Adams, engineers and surveyors. 1934 Feb. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Map of Easterly Part of Farm. [1915]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Tree Damage Areas Duke Farms. Thomas D. Van Syckel, Inc. undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., Basement Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., Front Elevation, Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., Rear Elevation, Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., First Floor Framing Plan, Second Floor Framing Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., Framing of Front Elevation, Framing of Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Cottage No. 3 Estate of J.B. Duke Esq., Framing of Rear Elevation, Framing of Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Topography at Life Camps Montague-Twp-Sussex Co.-NJ. Snook & Hardin, engineers. 1938 Nov 1. Linen. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Survey at Montague Township Made for The New Jersey Title Guarantee and Trust Company Property of Life Camps. Snook & Hardin, engineers. 1938 Aug 5. Linen. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Conservation Plan Map, Greenfield Plantation. Soil Conservation Service. 1965 Aug 11. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - [Duke Estates and Roadways], C-1, 13&14. undated. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - [Duke Estates and Roadways], D-7 13. undated. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - [Duke Estates and Roadways], D-7 14. undated. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Route 206 Princeton to Somerville, Sheet No. 13. Louis Berger & Associates. Undated. Diazo with colored pencil. (Oversize-folder DF1)
    - Hillsborough Township Map. Queale and Lynch, professional planners. 1978. Diazo with pen. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Fountain Basin, Duke's Farms. Buckenham and Miller, landscape architects. 1910 Jan 10. Pen drawing on vellum. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Mounded and prepared bed at Duke Farms. Undated. Ink and colored pencil on vellum. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Crop plans at Duke Farms. 1981, 1983, 1984, 1993 and undated. Diazo with colored pen. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Road Map Township of Hillsborough. Van Note/Harvey Associates. Undated. Diazo with red pencil. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Political Subdivisions of New Jersey and Major Highway Networks. New Jersey Department of Transportation. 1974. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Farm Map of Hillsboro, Surveyed & published by Matthew Hughes, 1860. 1976. Poster reproduction. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Panel Assembly. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, 6-DHB-St'd. Floor Plan. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Concrete Block Foundation. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Solid Concrete Foundation. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Top of Lactorium Roof. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Drain System for 6-DHB Lactorium. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - 6-DHB-Lactorium Building, Foundation Floor Plan 6-DHB. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF2)
    - Duke Farms Main Switchboard Rear View Wiring. Westinghouse Electric & Mfg. Co. 1939 Sep 11. Blueprint; diazo. (Oversize-folder DF3)
    - Duke Farms Underground Crossing of C.R.R. of N.J. Tracks. 1957 May 22. Blueprint; ink. (Oversize-folder DF3)
    - Maps of Boundbrook, NJ. US Dept of Interior/US Dept of Army Corps of Engineers. 1955. Color map. (Oversize-folder DF3)
    - Topographical Survey of Duke Farms (A-2 through A-6, B-1 through B-6, C-1 through C-6, D-1 through D-5, E-2, E-3). Richard H. Shindler, professional engineer and land surveyor. 1967 Mar. Negative Photostat. (Oversize-folder DF4)
    - Aerial view Saxton Falls and Musconetcong River. Robins Aerial Surveys, Inc. 1966 Oct 3. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Elevation of Fire Escape by Big Barn, Duke's Farm. P.C. Van Nuys, architect. Undated. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Plan of Fire Escape by Greenhouse, Fire Escape & Section of Bathroom. P.C. Van Nuys, architect. Undated. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Fire Escape at Big Barn, Duke's Farm. J.W. Fiske Iron Works. 1929 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Fire Escape by Green House, Duke's Farm. J.W. Fiske Iron Works. 1929 Aug 2. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., Basement Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., Front Elevation, Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., Rear Elevation, Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., First and Second Floor Framing Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., Framing of Front Elevation and Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Cottage No. 2, Estate of J.B. Duke, Esq., Framing of Rear Elevation and Side Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Aug 1. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF5)
    - Crop Plan, 1985. Diazo with colored pencil. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Proposed Metal Roof for Main Residence of Duke Farms. Donald Pantel, architect. 1966 Aug 24. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Revised Map of Survey Duchess Property, Tax Map Lot 14, Block 144. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1969 Jul 30. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Revised Map of Survey Olghart Property, Tax Map Lot 18, Block 144 & Lot 3, Block 48. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1969 Jul 30. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Map of Survey Adams Associates Property, Tax Map Lot 13, Block 144. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1969 Jul 30. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Map of Survey Lengyel Property, Tax Map Lot 10, Block 144. Donald H. Stires Associates. 1972 Jul 31. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Map of Survey, Portion of Lot 3 Block 142. George Riehman, surveyor. 1984 Oct 3. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Map showing road system and outer bounds of Duke Farms. Undated. Positive photostat with colored ink. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Zoning Map Readington Township. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF6)
    - Map of Raritan. 1856 Aug. Paper on linen. (Oversize-folder DF7)
    - Map of Survey Land to be Conveyed to Pete E. Cooley situated in Hillsborough Township, Somerset County, New Jersey. Donald H. Stires, professional engineer, land surveyor. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Location of Inlets on Abandoned Roads at Duke's Farms. Strait & Adams, engineers & surveyors. 1933 Jul. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mr. & Mrs. James H.R. Cromwell, Elevation of Window Adjoining Palm Room. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jul 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Map of Survey Showing Trees that Have Been Removed on Lot 4 Block 142, Hillsborough Twp. Cilo & Vliet, professional engineers & land surveyors. 1978 Sep 6. Positive Photostat. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Plan of Fountain Curbs for James B. Duke Esq. Buckenham and L.L. Miller, landscape engineers. 1910 Dec 14. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Fountain Basin Duke's Farm S'Ville, N.J., Showing pipe arrangements. Buckenham & Miller, landscape engineers. Revised to 1910 Mar 12. Ink on vellum. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Dukes Farm, Section No. 2 Woods East of Lodge (Beds No. 13-28). H. Buckenham & L.L. Miller, landscape engineers. Undated. Ink on linen. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Dukes Farm, Plantations in woods East of Lodge, Section No. 1 Equals Area South of Brook (Beds No. 1-12). H. Buckenham & L.L. Miller, landscape engineers. Undated. Ink on linen. (Oversize-folder DF8)
    - Sketch Showing Proposed Relocation of the County Highway at Duke Farms. Strait & Adams, Engineers & Surveyors. 1933 Oct. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., First Floor Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Foundation Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jun Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Second Floor Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Front Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Rear Elevation. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Roof Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Half Stall Room Elevation, Half Wagon Room Elevation, Section thro' Wagon Room, Part Elevation, Section thro' Stall Room. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Longitudinal Section. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jun. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Second Floor Framing. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., 1/2 Roof Truss Plan, 1/2 Roof Framing Plan. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Half Elevation of Wing Gables, Gables Over End Doors. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 May. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., 1/2 in. Detail of Stone Gable & Cupola. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. 1906 Jun Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Truss Details, [Sheet "A"], Transversal View of Trussels A-B. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Truss Details, [Sheet "B"], Half Elevation of Truss "I-J", Half Elevation of Truss E-F. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Truss Details, [Sheet "C"], Elevation of Truss K-L, Half Elevation of Truss G-H. Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Farm Barn for J.B. Duke, Esq., Elevation of Truss "C-D". Kendall Taylor & Stevens. [1906 May]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder DF9)
    - Duke Farms, Fountain System Upgrade-1984. C. Meyn, A. Jarveia. 1984 May. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF10)
    - Duke Farms, Fountain System Upgrade-Revised; includes Notes and Bill of Material. C. Meyn. 1984 Jun. Diazo. (Oversize-folder DF10)